Keep runnin' along.
Watch as we pass by.
As we raise our flag.
Up high in the sky.
Alright, here we go now.
Sailing through the endless ocean.
Facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure.
Nobody has ever.
Got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep
believing in our dreams.
And let our heart lead the way.
Then once we got all that.
All there's left is to go.
When we face the dark and stormy weather.
Keep the pace.
We'll link our hearts together.
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what.
Keep running along, keep running along.
Still raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to none.
We won't back down from anyone.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
Toward our own dreams
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal.
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world.
Start me up.
Keep running along, keep running along.
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top.
There's no way that we'll ever quit.
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
I see through your eyes,
what we'll have to face.
All the memories will stay in our hearts.
We'll never let them go.
Brand new world.
Let's start me up!
Yo-yo!
Boy, a lion shows no mercy.
Its fury remains for no creature.
I knew taking that second
rumble ball was a gamble,
but I was hoping it wouldn't be this bad.
Since I have seven different forms,
that means I only have a 14 %
chance of getting arm point.
but as long as i can move
i'll try as many times
as it takes that's right
i have to keep fighting
I can't let them down!
Come on, I'm point!
You won!
I'm point! You won!
Wrong again!
How many times is this going to take?
My body's about to give out on me.
I have to get arm point now!
Yo-yo-yay!
I got it!
When did that happen?
Beware yourself!
Your final attack!
It's all or nothing!
Glo-man!
Chouchou finger pistol!
Yeah!
This is my only chance!
I can't hold back!
Cloven!
Iron body strength!
Race Michietti!
That has to do it!
That was my strongest attack!
Splendid, ape, beautiful,
cherry blossom, blizzard.
Not yet.
Did I win?
You have awakened the wrath of heaven!
Feel the thunder of the lions roar!
Roar!
Tempest Kick Lotus!
This is it.
I don't have the strength
to fight back anymore.
Chopper?
Chopper, what in the world
did you do out there?
I don't remember.
Isn't gonna cut it.
This is serious. You know?
You're lucky no one died.
While you've been here sleeping,
the whole country's been in an
uproar about what you did last night.
What am I supposed to tell them?
I did something really bad, huh?
An entire village almost got wiped out.
I know you love your experiments
just like your old man,
but you have to plan these things
very carefully before you jump in.
Those are the rules.
A whole village wiped out?
You wouldn't think it at first, but you're
the spitting image of that crazy quack.
You can't help but
cause a ruckus, can you?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Please, Dr. E.
I promise I won't do it again,
so don't kick me out, okay?
You fool.
Just hurry up and get better already.
These chores aren't gonna do themselves.
Life return!
Hermine!
Suffer as you must, but do not cry.
For if you shed a tear, thy
name as a man shall suffer too!
He's going to kill me.
Far behind you is the peaceful mountain
village where the cicadas sing.
The sweet memories leaping in your heart
have given way to the
dancing flames of hell!
Licking at your feet with every
step of your final journey.
I give to you the leaves of a willow tree
dyed in crimson to honor your parting now
take it take it and
never look back see the
leaves fluttering in
Red Song of the Willow!
This is the end.
Robin. No.
I can't give up yet.
He escaped from the Hermine!
Rumble.
I'm sorry, Dr. E.
If I'm going to die
anyway, I have to try it.
Everyone, please stay away.
I'm about to lose control.
I used three rumble balls.
And then, I don't know,
I lost consciousness.
What happened?
I suppose you could say
your Devil Fruit went wild.
I don't care what happens.
You can't let yourself go down that path.
A power that destroys your foes,
but turns you against your
friends and your own body as well.
There's only one word
for a creature like that.
A monster.
Oh, crap.
Oh doesn't even matter that I'm super right
now this week has kicked my ass? Ragged
I'm
walking
away with his key number
four huh don't the
swordsman in the nose need
number two that's what
the deer said if this
guy at number four and that guy at number
three well that narrows things down some
that can only mean that
secretary looking gal
has the number two key I better hurry up
and find her those guys
really need my help!
I was under the impression
that you were short on time.
If that were the case, it would
seem you aren't trying very hard.
But perhaps this is all part of your plan.
Don't you mock me.
You'll pay for this.
Sounds great.
I'm ready when you are.
You don't have to wait for me, you know.
The battle has already started, after all.
Arrogant, aren't you?
I mean, you ate a Devil Fruit.
So that bath is disabling your power.
If your body's half-submerged, I
can't imagine you can do much damage.
Oh, yeah?
You think I'm so cocky I'd drop my guard?
Don't worry about me.
Even without my powers, I'm
still better off than you.
Pardon me a moment.
Just what the hell did you do to me?
It would spoil it if I told you now.
Solving that mystery is part of
the fun of fighting a powerholder.
Whatever it was that happened to Sanji,
she's obviously the one who's behind it.
I've got to be careful, otherwise
I'll end up just like him.
I'm finally starting to
get some strength back
So you think I'm weak, huh?
Well, you haven't seen the
perfect climb attack yet.
If you think I'm just a pretty
face, you're in for a world of hurt!
I can move my legs.
Here it comes!
Thunder! Charge!
Free my arm!
That's an impressive weapon.
Are those clouds?
Did you think I'd just lie
there and let you stomp on me?
Here's my thunderbolt.
Tupo!
And that's what happens when
you don't take me seriously.
What an interesting surprise I never
thought I'd get struck by lightning indoors.
Damn that barrier protected
her but what was it
made of it looked like
it turned into bubbles.
You better hurry and figure that out
it's your only chance of defeating me!
I shouldn't tease you like that.
You'll never guess.
It was almost like soap
when you washed it away.
Did you eat some kind
of bubble bubble fruit?
Is that it?
Well, still,
even if you do know what my power does,
that doesn't mean you're
stronger than me or anything.
Understand?
Talk about defensive.
I almost feel bad for her.
To put it one way, my
power is cleanliness.
I'm a soap human, thanks
to the bubble bubble fruit,
so my entire body produces a lather.
Lovely, isn't it? Whoa!
How sexy!
I wish I had a secretary like her!
Wait, I'm talking like an old man!
Uh, it seems pretty useless
for fighting, though.
So what, do you make people slip?
The sea of bubbles that I
create obey my every command,
and I have quite the imagination. Hm?
What the?
I'll give you an example.
So she wasn't just taking a bath.
Bubble master, soap sheep.
What?
Beautiful, huh?
Yeah, some imagination.
Don't let the fluffy appearance fool you.
Sheep cloud, relaxing bubbles.
Oh,
by the way, didn't you wonder why you lost
your strength when you walked in here?
Of course.
That must have had something
to do with her power.
What else could it be?
Now that I think about it,
when I came through the door...
The floor was covered with bubbles.
Oh, crap!
You took too long to figure it out.
My strength is fading again.
It's just like earlier when I
stepped on that puddle of bubbles.
Give it some time!
You'll soon understand the
true horror of this power.?
The bubbles that come
from my body are thorough.
They scour and clean
anything you can think of.
Dirt and general filth, of course.
As well as your strength.
Perhaps you need to be
reminded of something.
I'm not just a secretary.
I'm one of the world's
most deadly assassins.
I can move again.
Maybe it's because the
bubbles disappeared.
I'm done with your crap. Thunder!
That weapon is interesting,
but it won't be enough.
Golden bubble!
What are you doing?
My legs, I can't stand.
What'd you, what'd you do to me?
Pretty, aren't they?
My lightest touch can
make anything glistened.
It's my gift to make everything beautiful.
I'll give your skin a luminescent sheen.
Every inch of your body
will shimmer from my touch.
Once in a man's life!
Once in a man's life,
he encounters a foe that
his honor demands he face,
even though it might result in his demise.
Save Domestic Lotus!
Cry out, Song of Willow!
Oh, my God.
I got no idea what kind of
chunk is waiting for me.
As soon as I get back up,
I better get me some cola.
All right.
I wonder if that deer is
still hanging in there.
What's going on up there?
What the hell is that?
Wait, that's the CP9 guy that
got locked in the fridge.
That thing's holding him like a ragdoll.
What the hell did I miss?
That hat!
I think it's the same style
that deer was wearing!
Hey, you!
You're not that deer gorilla, right?
This can't be real.
No, it's him, all right.
It's Kumadori.
His body came rocketing
over from the Tower of Law.
But who could have done that to him?
Seriously, what the hell is this problem?
A voice?
Hey, keep moving.
I don't remember telling
you to stop, Nico Robin.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Don't forget who's the boss here.
All right, Luchi.
Just drag her.
Pull her by the hair if you have to.
It's an order.
Now come on.
Start walking.
You're delusional, aren't you? Oh my.
You're honestly convinced that the Straw
Hats are still on their way to rescue you.
I've never seen such a
weak-looking pirate crew.
If that's your only
hope, that's pretty sad.
That explosion we heard earlier was
probably the pipes or something.
There's no way they
could make it this far.
While you're up in your little fantasy
world dreaming of being rescued,
we'll pass the Gates of Justice.
The Bridge of Hesitation lies
right before the Gates of Justice.
We'll cross the first
elevated half of the bridge,
and once the gates are within our sight,
The other half of the bridge
will rise from the sea,
and then we'll finally pass
through the gates themselves.
Once the gates are firmly closed behind
us, every lingering trace of your pathetic,
misguided optimism will
be dashed to pieces.
You'll forget what hope even means.
The only feeling left in your body will be
an overwhelming and
eternal sense of guilt.
You will spend your days in ceaseless
atonement for your arrogant crime of existing.
You know it's true, Nico. Robin.
Now then, hurry along.
Move your feet, wench.
ROBIN! ROBIN!
What was that?
I heard someone!
Did you hear that?
Who was it?
You better take Nico
Robin and start moving.
Don't worry, Chief.
I'll handle this.
The door!
At least it doesn't look like
it's made of iron this time!
It's big in here!
Where am I?
I found you, pigeon bastard!
Glad you could make it.